
hi, how are you doing?	im fine. how about yourself? im fine. how about yourself? im pretty good. thanks for asking. im pretty good. thanks for asking. no problem. so how have you been? no problem. so how have you been? ive been great. what about you? ive been great. what about you? ive been good. im in school right now. ive been good. im in school right now. what school do you go to? what school do you go to? i go to pcc. i go to pcc. do you like it there? do you like it there? its okay. its a really big campus. its okay. its a really big campus. good luck with school. good luck with school. thank you very much. hows it going im doing well. how about you? im doing well. how about you? never better, thanks. never better, thanks.	so how have you been lately? so how have you been lately? ive actually been pretty good. you? ive actually been pretty good. you? im actually in school right now. im actually in school right now. which school do you attend? which school do you attend? im attending pcc right now. im attending pcc right now.	are you enjoying it there? are you enjoying it there?	its not bad. there are a lot of people there. its not bad. there are a lot of people there.	good luck with that.good luck with that.	thanks. how are you doing today?	im doing great. what about you?im doing great. what about you?	im absolutely lovely, thank you.im absolutely lovely, thank you.	everythings been good with you?everythings been good with you?	i havent been better. how about yourself?i havent been better. how about yourself?	i started school recently.i started school recently.	where are you going to school?where are you going to school?	im going to pcc.imgoing to pcc.	how do you like it so far?how do you like it so far?	i like it so far. my classes are pretty good right now.i like it so far. my classes are pretty good right now.	i wish you luck.its an ugly day today.	i know. i think it may rain.i know. i think it may rain.	its the middle of summer, it shouldnt rain today.its the middle of summer, it shouldnt rain today.	that would be weird.that would be weird.	yeah, especially since its ninety degrees outside.yeah, especially since its ninety degrees outside.	i know, it would be horrible if it rained and it was hot outside.i know, it would be horrible if it rained and it was hot outside.	yes, it would be. 